{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": " You ___ help me if you don't have time. I can do the job myself.",
            "a": "  aren't able to",
            "b": "  don't have to",
            "c": " mustn't",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " ___ you help me?",
            "a": " May",
            "b": "  Shall",
            "c": "  Will",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " You ___ go into that room. It's forbidden!",
            "a": " don't have to",
            "b": "  mustn't",
            "c": "  might not",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " It's 2:20 and he said he'd be here at 2:30. He ___ be here soon.",
            "a": "  should",
            "b": "  can",
            "c": " would",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " I have a headache. ___ you buy some aspirin for me?",
            "a": " Shall",
            "b": "  May ",
            "c": "  Could",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " There are no lights on and no one answers the doorbell. They ___ be at home.",
            "a": "  must not",
            "b": "  cannot",
            "c": " will not",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " I ___ come to your party. I have to work.",
            "a": " shouldn't",
            "b": "  must not",
            "c": "  can't",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " ___ I make some coffee? I'll do it if you'll drink a cup.",
            "a": "  Must",
            "b": "  Shall",
            "c": " Ought",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " You ___ seen her in Chicago! I know for a fact that she wasright here in Phoenix!",
            "a": "  must have",
            "b": " should not have",
            "c": "  couldn't have",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": " Yes, I know that I ___ studied last night, but I decided towatch TV instea",
            "a": " would have",
            "b": "  should have",
            "c": " must have",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "1",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}